Guide to the Janet G. Travell papers, 1910-1997 MS0704.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- White House years, 1950-1997; MS0704 Series 5; 6.5 Linear feet (Box 84, Box 82, Box 83, Box 80, Box 81, Box 78, Box 79, Box 75, Box 74, Box 77, Box 76, Box 73, Box 72)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - H, 1961-1964 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - I, 1961-1962 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - J, 1961-1964 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - K, 1961-1965 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - L, 1961-1963 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - M, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Meharry Medical College, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - N, 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - O, 1961-1964 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - P, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Phi Beta Kappa, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - R, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - S, 1961-1965 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - T, 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - V, 1962-1964 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - W, 1961-1965 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1964 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Including much relating to Kennedy's rocking chair
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House interoffice memoranda, 1961-1964 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - White House, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Y, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence - Z, 1961-1964 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and Clippings - White House years and beyond (including Merryfield Farm Joint Venture), 1961-1997 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and clippings about Speaker Sam Rayburn, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and Clippings regarding Dr. Travell's time in the White House, 1961-1965 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and clippings related to White House years, 1950-1989 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and clippings related to White House years, 1950-1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence and lease for home at 3319 N Street, NW, Washington, DC, 1961-1965 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence from people asking for medical help/advice, 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence from people asking for medical help/advice, 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence from people asking for medical help/advice, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence from people asking for medical help/advice, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence on rocking chairs, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence on rocking chairs, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Correspondence on rocking chairs, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Correspondence on rocking chairs, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Correspondence regarding advertisement for "Spray Pain Away", 1962 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Correspondence regarding Awards, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Correspondence regarding chair design, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Correspondence with Foreign Students, 1961-1963 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Correspondence with Lewis Deschler (Parliamentarian, U.S. House of Representatives) regarding statute authorizing Physician to the White House, 1961-1967 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Correspondence with organizations, 1961-1963 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Correspondence with Otis Air Force Base, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Letters to Dr. Travell from students, 1961-1964 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Letters to Dr. Travell from students, 1961-1964 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Requests for books and possible writing projects, 1961-1965 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Requests for reprints by Dr. Travell, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Rocking chairs - correspondence and articles, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: White House Correspondence and Press Releases, etc., 1961-1965 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: White House Correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Article about Dr. Travell in Modern Medicine magazine, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Certificates and miscellaneous correspondence, 1963-1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    Including clippings on President Kennedy's assassination
  - White House Years: Christmas cards and articles, 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Clippings about John Kennedy, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Clippings about John Kennedy, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Clippings about John Kennedy, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Clippings about John Kennedy, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Clippings and articles about Dr. Travell, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Clippings on Kennedy assassination and autopsy, 1965-1966 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: Esquire article on Dr. Travell, 11/1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Essay Contest "The Role of the Community in the Employment of the Handicapped", 1962 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Family Weekly magazine article on Travell, 04/29/1962 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: "First Woman Physician" article, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: J.J. Keegan Anatomical slides (photo prints), Life magazine, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Newspaper clippings - Summer of 1961 to Spring 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Newspaper clippings of Dr. Travell's White House years, 1961-1963 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Requests for Dr. Travell to write magazine articles, 1961-1964 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Saturday Evening Post article on Dr. Travell, 10/21/1961 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Sports Illustrated article on Dr. Travell, 04/03/1961 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: U.S. News & World Report, magazine, 02/20/1961 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    Includes article on Travell and pain relief
  - White House Years: White House articles on President's health, 1961-1965 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - White House Years: White House clippings, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - White House Years: Aerospace Seating, 1961-1965 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - White House Years: Burkley, George - Assistant White House Physician, 1961-1964 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - White House Years: Canceled tour of U.S. Air Force and Army hospitals in Europe, 04/1963 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - White House Years: Furniture Requests, 1961-1964 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - White House Years: Lady Bird Johnson's trip to Cleveland, 04/20/1964 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - White House Years: Mattresses for Kennedy's, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - White House Years: Mental Retardation, 1961-1965 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - White House Years: Mental Retardation, 1961-1965 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Moving to Washington - Resignation as President Johnson's Physician, 1961-1965 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Narcotics and Drug Abuse, 1962-1964 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Notes/Telephone messages, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Obesity Measurements, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Panel on Mental Retardation, 1961-1964 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Physical Fitness, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - White House Years: Receipts - White House and other, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - White House Years: Requests for Photographs, 1961-1964 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - White House Years: Safety and accident prevention, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - White House Years: Shoes, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - White House Years: Telephone Calls, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - White House Years: Transcript of news conference with Pierre Salinger and Dr. Travell regarding President, undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - White House Years: Kennedy's illness, 06/22/1961 -06/23/1961 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - White House Years: Travel by Dr. Travell, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - White House Years: Vellore Christian Medical College & Hospital - India, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - White House Years: White House swimming pool, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - White House Years: World Health Organization, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 01/1961 -05/1961 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 06/1961 -09/1961 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 10/1961 -12/1961 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 01/1962 -06/1962 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 01/1962 -06/1962 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 07/1962 -12/1962 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 07/1962 -12/1962 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 1963-1965 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - White House Years: Invitations, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Galley proofs and manuscript drafts of Dr. Travell's books, 1915-1994; MS0704 Series 6; 6.5 Linear feet (Box 90, Box 91, Box 88, Box 89, Box 86, Box 87, Box 84, Box 85, Box 97, Box 96, Box 95, Box 94, Box 93, Box 92)
  This series contains manuscript drafts and galley proofs of Dr. Travell's autobiography "Office Hours: Day and Night" and galley proofs of "Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual." Within the chapter draft folders for her autobiography are included correspondence and notes related to her childhood. These materials date from 1915-94 with the bulk of the material falling within 1966-91.
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Atlanta book tour, 01/21/1969 -01/23/1969 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Bibliography for Office Hours: Day and Night, 1968ca. (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Book chapter "Management of Myofascial Pain Syndrome", 1986 -1987 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Book Jacket for Office Hours: Day and Night, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Book party for Office Hours: Day and Night, 12/12/1968 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Books Interviews, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: California tour to promote Dr. Travell's autobiography, 03/1969 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Cleveland, Ohio tour to promote Dr. Travell's autobiography, 02/1969 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence - galley proof corrections with NAL Publishers, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence - Responses to Office Hours: Day and Night, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence - Responses to Office Hours: Day and Night, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence - World Publishing Company, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence regarding permission to use copyrighted material in Office Hours: Day and Night, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Correspondence requesting permission to publish various items in Office Hours: Day and Night, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Dr. Travell and David Simons and the genesis of the Trigger Point Manual, 1972-1994 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1980 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1978-1981 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second edition of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second edition of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second edition of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second edition of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Table of Contents, Chapter 1, Index, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 2, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 3, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 4, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 5, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 5, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 6, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 7, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 8, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 9-10, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume (1983) of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 10 and Chapter 9, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 11, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 11-13, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 12-13, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 16, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 17-18, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 19, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 20, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 21-23, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 24-25, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 26-27, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 27-28, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 29-31, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 32, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 34, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 36, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 36-37, undated (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapters 44-49, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for first volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons - Chapter 45 and Chapter 15, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Galley Proofs and Manuscript Drafts: Galley proofs and illustrations for second volume of Myofascial Pain and Dysfunction: The Trigger Point Manual, co-authored by David Simons, 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 6)